live like say welcome brothers and
sisters to another Wednesday question
and answer well we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
world to keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage thou shall
have no other gods before me thou has
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above
or that is in the earth beneath or that
is in the water under the Earth thou
shall not bow down thyself to them nor
serve them for I the Lord thy God am a
jealous God visiting the iniquity of the
fathers upon the children until the
third and fourth generation of them that
hate me and showing Mercy unto thousands
of them that love me and keep my
Commandments thou sh not take the name
of the Lord thy God in vain for the Lord
will not hold him Guiltless that take up
his name in vain remember the Sabbath
day to keep it holy six days shall th
lab and do all thy work but the seven
day he is the Sabbath of the Lord thy
God and it thou shall not do any work
thou nor thy son nor thy daughter thy
man servant nor thy maid servant nor thy
cattle or thy stranger that is within
thy gates for in six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and resteth the seventh day
wherefore the Lord bless the Sabbath day
and HED unto thy father and thy mother
that thy days may be long upon the land
which the Lord thy God given thee thou
shall not kill thou sh not commit
adultery thou shall not steal thou shall
not bear false witness against thy
neighbor thou sh not cover thy
neighbor's house thou not covered thy
neighbor's wife nor his man servant nor
his maid servant nor his Ox nor his ass
nor anything that is thy neighbors ReRe
Exodus 21-17 and may the Lord have a
blessing to to the reading of his words
in Jesus name we pray amen amen amen so
he on question an answer you can ask us
a question and we'll answer it according
to the King James Bible and if we cannot
find the answer we will seek further
counsel to bring you an answer at a
later time keep in mind that all vague
questions will not be answered and all
long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we may be
able to point you in the direction of a
DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling office so please be as direct as
possible with your questions so we can
be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you may begin to
send in your questions even questions
that pertain to everlasting life we
asking that you just keep your questions
to a maximum of two scriptures let me
introduce to you the family that'll be
on the panel this evening you got
brother Dre good evening brother Julius
good evening everybody brother Jerome
gra and peace Brother tanzel good
evening sister
Deborah good
evening and we have Casey with us and
the guest caller and I'm brother Cornell
sister Deborah what is our first
question of the evening yes there are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A so uh Israelite by Blood
Brandon says in Luke
24:36 was used to stay Christ didn't
rise can you all please give me more
understanding because the understanding
that I have is that Christ's body did
didn't see
corruption all right so brother Jerome
about this Christ didn't rise can you
please shed some light on that so it's
Luke 24 verse
36 yeah I'm G show you that the um the
11 Apostles disagree with that mindset
but let's go read the verse um verse 36
when you get it Tel go ahead and read it
and as they thus spake Jesus himself
stood in the midst of them and said unto
them peace be unto you okay now go right
skip up to verse 33 and read it into the
36 and it'll let you know the apostles
the 11 they believe he rose go ahead and
read it and they rose up the same hour
and returned to Jerusalem and found the
11 gathered together and them that were
with them saying the Lord is risen
indeed and have appeared to
Simon they say the Lord has risen indeed
that's what they said okay well they
didn't believe it initially but
eventually yeah they believe he rose go
ahead and they told what things were
done in the way and how he was known of
them in Breaking of
bread and as they thus spake Jesus
himself stood in the midst of them and
said unto them peace be unto you yeah he
didn't open no door he just popped up in
the where they was go ahead and read
that verse 37 but they were terrified
and the frighten and supposed that they
have seen the spirit yeah because at
that time when he rose from the dead he
was a spirit being he wasn't Flesh and
Blood no more that's right now this deal
with the part of the question that says
uh Christ body uh didn't seek corruption
you can find that in Acts the second
chapter so let's go there Acts chapter 2
verse
30-32 when you get it go ahead and
read therefore being in prophet and
knowing that God has sworn with Ino to
him that of the fruit of his Lo
according to the flesh he would raise up
Christ to sit on his
throne and he seen this before spake of
the resurrection of Christ that his soul
was not left in Hell neither his flesh
did see corruption mhm
his soul was left in the grave hell in
this case is the grave neither did his
body seek corruption he was in the in
the sepa for three days and three nights
that's right that's all I think that's
in Psalms 16 chapter 2 okay all right
yes sir thank you for that brother
Jerome if there was no Resurrection then
we don't need no Bible do
we all right hope that answered your
question is we move on to our
next yes uh shot says if there are only
two
resurrections at Christ second coming
and after the Thousand-Year rest what
took place after Christ was crucified in
Matthew
27 ver 52 and
53 all right it was two resurrections
pick up from there brother Julius on
that Matthew
2752 and
53 let's go to uh tenzel and read that
there are two
resurrections there's only two
resurrections and as you stated in your
question at Christ coming but these two
resurrections are the resurrection of
the dead and they both will be F or
Spirit beings when they come out those
Graves let's look at this scripture
Matthew
27 and pick it up with this time we G to
pick it up we going to go a little
higher we're gonna go a little bit
higher pick it up at verse uh this is
when Jesus died 50 verse 50 go
ahead and Jesus when he had cried again
with a loud voice yielded up The
Ghost and behold the veil of the temple
was written Twain from the top of the
bottom and the Earth did quake and the
rocks ran go ahead and the graves were
open and many bodies of the saints were
slept arose and many bodies of the
Saints which slept arose it didn't say
they came out them grave Spirit beings
go ahead and came out of the graves
after his resurrection and went into the
holy city oh they came out to the Grave
after his resurrection right after Jesus
resurrected when Jesus resurrected as
Jerome just said he appeared just po and
appeared and went through doors and and
appeared to people Flesh and Blood can't
do that so when Jesus resurrected he was
a spirit being these people was
resurrected back to flesh and blood and
it was in that area so when the Lord
come back well continue to
read and went into the holy city and
appeared unto many it was in that area
and for what reason go ahead now when
the centurions and they that were with
him watching Jesus saw the earthquake
wait and those things that were done
they feared greatly saying truly truly
this was the son of God because it was
prophesied that he would be in the grave
in Matthew the 12th chapter ver 38-40
for three days and three nights he went
into the grave of Flesh and Blood being
stayed three days and three nights
resurrected and came out a spirit
being a spirit being so now the people
here was they came after the grave after
his resurrection and they went back into
Jerusalem in that area and they were
flesh and blood they eventually died
again the first resurrection does not
take place until the Lord
come that's why the book say blessed are
those that take part in the first
resurrection because they going to be
Spirit beard they're going to be God and
after a thousand years the rest of the
Dead come back and they going to be
spirit being spirit being sisters and
brothers but the bottom line is Who
resurrection this Resurrection here was
a miracle to show who he was to show his
power but these people were resurrected
back to Flesh and Blood I hope that
helped all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer question by the
way Corel oh I'm sorry by the way if you
go to um Matthew the 10th chapter and
verse
7 it it tell you real quick he tells you
uh at verse Matthew 10 real quick look
what he told his
disciples this wasn't new raising the
dead wasn't new Jesus gave them
power Matthew
10:6 when you get it go
ahead but go rather to the lost sheep of
the House of
Israel go ahead and as he go preaching
saying the Kingdom of Heaven is at hand
meaning he himself an ambassador go
ahead heal the sick heal the sick the
lepers yes raise the Dead Oh raise the
dead go ahead cast out Devils yep freely
ye have received freely give so you have
Peter them that can raise the dead Jesus
raised a little girl and said give us
something to eat right so you got all
kinds of um people being resurrected but
this was not the first resurrection I
hope that helped right right yeah all
right thank you for that as we move on
to our next question yes Peter Israel
says looking at the typo in Genesis 14
verse4 the land of Dan is this the
correct name in
Joshua 19 verse 47
lashem all right gu caller can you share
some light on this Genesis 14 and4
guys caller you with
us yeah let's go read
it Genesis 14 and verse 14 is the first
one then we got Joshua 19 and 47 so
start off the 14 and
14 and when Abram heard that his brother
was taken captive he armed in his
trained servants born in his own house
318 and pursued them unto
Dan now no Dan hadn't even been born yet
in fact uh uh Isaac hadn't been born
Israel hadn't been born you know Jacob
brother and Dan is one of the sons of
Jacob so this wasn't a typo what it was
the translators and they translated the
Bible they knew what the new name of
this land was called it was called Dan
which is named after the tribe uh after
the uh uh uh Jacob's son Dan now let's
get go down to uh
Joshua
1947 was that 19 and uh 47
right and the coast of the children of
Dan went out too little for them
therefore the children of Dan went up to
fight against Le and took it and smoked
it with the edge of the sword and
possessed it and dwelt therein and
called lean Dan after the name of Dan
their
father see now that wasn't the name of
the land when Abraham was around so then
that's most likely could have been the
original name you know which is
ation but uh then it was I knew it was
the translators because the same
translators missed up with the uh uh
with the Lord when he told Moses that My
Name by my he said your fathers known me
as the god of Abraham the god of Isaac
and the god of Jacob but by my name
Jehovah was I not known but then when
Abraham got ready to uh sacrifice
Isaac and then he he called in name of
Jehovah back then so but in the
meantime he said the Lord God there but
the translators knew was he his name was
Jo Jehovah by the time they translated
the Bible so these are
translation uh I don't say called error
I call them translation
updates okay so now that was most likely
the name nation was most likely the name
because
uh there no other scripture that say was
called anything else until Dan came and
changed it that's all I have to say all
right hope that answers your question
there we continue to move on to our
next yes moving on Zion asks who are the
ones that will be in the first
resurrection are they the ones that had
died in their righteousness and will be
caught up in the air with Jesus when he
returns
so who are the ones that will be in the
first resurrection are they the ones
that have died in their righteousness
yes that's some of them that will be
there part of that first resurrection
but also the living will also partake in
that first resurrection let's go to
first Thessalonians the 4th
chapter and let's pick it up when you
get
there at that verse 14
because if we believe that Jesus died
and rose again and walk in his ways hey
whether you dead or living you'll be a
part of that first resurrection pick it
up at that verse um 14 go
ahead for if for if we believe that
Jesus died and rose again even so them
also which sleep in Jesus will God bring
with them yes so those which sleep in
Jesus the ones that have already died go
ahead for this we say unto you by the
word of the Lord
that we which are alive and remain unto
the coming of the Lord shall not prevent
them which are asleep no for the Lord
himself shall descend from heaven with a
shout with the voice of the Archangel
and with the Trump of God and the dead
in Christ shall rise first so then the
dead in Christ the ones that have died
they're going to rise first in their
righteousness go ahead then we which are
alive and remain shall be caught up
together with them in the clouds to meet
the Lord in the air and so shall we ever
be with the Lord yes and that will
definitely be down on Earth after we
meet him in the clouds then we coming
back down to the Earth there'll be no
going to heaven as man is taught but it
will be the living and the dead that
will be a part of that first
resurrection and not the dead only right
that's all I
get and we hope that that answers your
question question and we're going to
keep moving right along sister yes
moving on ran 64 says in the wilderness
where it says in the Bible people should
go under the rod what does this really
mean going under that Rod Dre what does
it really mean let's go to uh Ezekiel
the 20th chapter and take a look at that
Ezekiel 20 and we're going to pick it up
at verse 35
Ezekiel 20 and 35 go ahead and read it
when you get it
tanel and I will bring you into the
Wilderness of the people and there will
I plead with you face to face like as I
pleaded with your fathers in the
wilderness of the land of Egypt so what
I plead with you say the Lord
God I will cause you to pass under the
rod and I will bring you into the bond
of the Covenant yes sir go ahead and I
will Purge out from among you the Rebels
and them that transgress against me and
I will bring them forth out of the
country where they sourn and they shall
not enter into the land of Israel and ye
shall know that I am the Lord he say he
gonna bring you into the Wilderness and
he gonna P cause you to pass under this
rod and this Rod is going to be a rod of
chastisement are Rod also that gathers
and and deals with you and separates the
the good from the bad this is part of
that purging process and verse 38 he
says I will Purge out from among you the
rebels let's look at it one more time
let's go to uh Matthew 25 and pick it up
at 31 Matthew 25 and
31 Matthew 25 and 31 yes sir read
31-33 and when the son of man shall come
in his glory and all the Holy Angels
with him then shall he sit upon the
throne of his
glory and before him shall be gathered
all nations he shall separate them one
from another and as a Shepherd divide of
his sheep the
goats he shall set the sheep on his
right hand but the goats on the left now
notice he's talking about the shepherd
dividing the sheep and the shepherd got
a Rob and and he
uh separates the goats from the Sheep so
will the Lord Purge out the rebels as
spoken in in Ezekiel 20 and when you
read in Psalm 23 says y though I walk
through the valley the Lord is my
shepherd and Y I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death I will fear no
evil for thou art with me thy rod and
thy staff they comfort me so if you if
you with God you ain't got nothing to
worry about in terms of being purged but
if you not you going to get
purged so that's all I got on that uh
brother Cornell yes sir yeah Lord ain't
gonna be taking no mess you gon do what
he say or you goon get some Rod right
Dre yes
sir all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our
next next one Glenn Sirus asked who are
the four horns and four carpenters in
Zechariah 1 vers
16 excuse me verses 18 through
21 all right so brother Jerome who are
these four carpenters in that
Zechariah well let's go read the verses
um Zechariah Chapter 1 Verse 18 through
you get it go ahead and read then lifted
up then lifted I up my eyes and saw and
behold for horns and I said unto the
angel that talk with me what be these
and he answered me these are the horns
which have scattered Judah Israel in
Jerusalem okay stop right stop right
there so I can answer about the horn
those uh horns mentioned in in verse
19 those
are the
Gentiles that scattered the Jews who
were still in the land at the time which
was three tribes they were referred to
as Jews uh Judah Benjamin and Levi and
these four Gentiles down through the
generations they scattered they
scattered those Jews you know I think it
was uh Babylon Meo Persia Greece
and Rome because the nine tribes are
already gone okay now let's read about
the uh let's keep reading so we can get
to the
Carpenters and the Lord showed me four
Carpenters then said I what come these
to do and he spake saying these are the
horns which have scattered Judah so that
no man did lift up his head but these I
come to freay them and to cast out the
horns of the Gentiles when lifted up
their horns over the land of Judah to
scatter
it okay so now the Carpenters are four
angels and those same Four Angels you
can read about them way in in
Revelations you know they holding back
the Four Winds and the Four Winds are
those four Gentile Nations that I was
talking about even up up until the time
of the uh Return of the Lord these four
Angels going to be holding these uh
these nations back these Gentiles these
four uh Nations the of the Gentiles you
know you're going to be holding back and
keeping them from getting into any major
conflict before the ready for the Lord
is ready for them to like World War I
for example he he holding them keeping
them at peace to the to the to the
degree where they don't really get into
major conflict flict
okay uh anybody want to add something
else they came that's all I got on why
don't you go to Revelation seven
chapter yeah of it thank
yeah Revelation 7 yeah one and
two
yeah and after these things I saw four
Angels standing on the four corners of
the Earth holding the Four Winds of the
Earth that the wind should not blow on
the earth nor on the sea nor on any
tree and I saw another Angel sending
from the East having the Seal of the
Living God and he cried with a loud
voice to the four angels to whom it was
given to hurt the
earth and the Sea yeah
yeah that's that's
all and further only will tell you these
four are to cast out the horns of the
Gentiles
that's
it all right thank you for that hope
that answers your question as we move on
to our next
question next question Vanessa Frederick
says in reference to the
Sonia Massie killing I heard someone say
that until Israel as a People starts
seeking God early and confessing our
sins only then will The Killing stop is
this
true brother Dre what you say Sonia
Madison killing was worldwide go ahead
brother yeah uh she was one among many
that are uh dying and being
killed and this thing is deeper than
that let's go to Deuteronomy the 30th
chapter
uh turning to
God it certainly wouldn't hurt us to do
so let's go to Deuteronomy 30 and pick
it up at verse one tanel when you get it
go ahead brother and it shall come to
pass when all these things I come upon
the come upon thee the blessing and the
curse which I have set before thee thou
shall call them to mind among all the
nations whether the Lord thy God ha
driven thee
and shall return unto the Lord thy God
and shall obey his voice according to
all that I command thee this day thou
and thy children with all thy heart and
with all thy soul that then the Lord thy
God will turn thy captivity and have
compassion upon thee and will return and
gather thee from all the nations whether
the Lord thy God have scattered thee so
the Lord promises to do this he didn't
say when though but if you do this he'll
be a little Sanctuary onto you in the
places where you've been scattered and
in that Sanctuary you can rest in him
but at the end of the day this thing
will continue to happen until the coming
of the Lord so it's not something that's
G to stop right there but he is going to
gather us and if you continue to read on
he'll tell you that re skip down to
verse six
and the Lord thy God will circumcise thy
heart and the Heart of thy seed to love
the Lord thy God with all thy heart and
with all thy soul that thou mayest live
and that's what will happen if we put
this word in our heart and in our mind
we circumcise our heart that we may love
the Lord Our God with all our heart and
all our soul that we may live not only
here but in the world to come but let's
go to Luke the 21st chapter Luke
21 Luke
21 and uh pick it up at
verse um 20 Luke
and look let's just get right to the
point read verse
24 and they shall fall by the edge of
the sword and shall be led away captive
into all Nations and Jerusalem shall be
trien down of the Gentiles until the
time of the Gentiles be fulfilled and
that's what's happening with Israel we
are Tren down of the Gentiles until the
times of the Gentiles be fulfilled and
that's when the Lord will gather us but
until that
time it's best to be under that little
Sanctuary by keeping his word that's all
I got on that if anybody want to add
hey Drake can we read that one verse out
of Deuteronomy 28 yes sir and verse 66
tzel when you get there because not only
Sonna Massi that they just mentioned
this is everybody just about Deuteronomy
28 and verse 66 tanzel go ahead and thy
life shall hang in doubt for thee thou
shall fear day and night and shall have
none Assurance of thy life
man we see that happening all the time
don't we when you have no Assurance of
your life people getting taken out all
the time it's gonna be that way like you
said brother until the Lord come back
and straighten it out that's
right all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
moving on Valencia asks you to explain
Exodus
30: 12 and
13 Exodus
30 vers 12 and 13 G
Calla let's go down and read
it Exodus 302 and 13 tanzel go right
ahead or thou taketh the Su of the
children of Israel after their number
then shall they give Every Man a ransom
for his soul unto the Lord and without
number ISD them that there be no plague
among them when thouest them this they
shall give everyone that pass among them
that are numbered half a shekele half
the shekele of the sanctuary a shekele
was 20
J did you stop at verse 13 oh we was I
was uh right in the middle of it okay go
ahead and half shekele shall be the
offering of the Lord
now this is Israel did a whole lot of
offering sin offering and they had like
this was just one of many offering where
you had to give the Lord amount ex
amount of money for the for The Ransom
of your soul but then that's
is anymore the reason is is because when
Jesus came he is the ransom now but
first let's go into Psalm chapter 49
Psalm chapter
49 and we going to read verses uh uh 1
through3 and we're going to skip now
67 and then 9 49 1-3 Psalms 49 read it
hear this all ye people give he all ye
inhabitants of the world both low and
high rich and poor together my mouth
shall speak of wisdom and the meditation
of my shall be of
understanding okay that's three skip
down to six and seven they that trust
and their wealth and boast themselves in
the multitude of their riches none of
them can by any means redeem his brother
nor give to God a ransom for him none by
any means can redeem his brother nor
give God a ransom for him skip down and
read verse
n that he should still live forever and
not see
corruption they they paid that Ransom
you know for uh uh for some type you
know offense but none of them could pay
give God a ransom
for his life eternal life except for one
let's go to Matthew the 20th chapter
read verses 27 and 28
Y and whosoever will be Chief among you
let him be your servant even as the son
of man came not to be Minister
unto but to minister and to give his
life a ransom for
many so that terminates
that Ransom that uh uh that Israel had
to pay because Jesus came and he gave
his life for ransom that we can all
receive the atonement that's all I have
to say yes all right thank you for that
sister deboras we move on with the time
check yes the time is
804 P for in Christ doesn't appear to
agree with
converts to our faith as Revelation 2
verse 9 and Revelation 3 verse 9 what
are your thoughts about converts
well Julius share some light I'm trying
to be I'm trying to figure out the name
of the person that's asking this
question and then or is there separating
Christ doesn't appear is that what
they're saying Christ doesn't appear to
agree with converts to our
faith well we're going to uh answer the
question
um it says uh doesn't appear to agree
with con to our faith as Revelation 2:9
re let's go to Revelation 2:9 and 3:9 it
has nothing to do with converts it has
something to do with identity
theft that the people who call
themselves uh Jews Revelation 29 and 39
when you get it read it tenzel I Know
Thy Works in Tribulation and poverty but
thou are rich and I know the blasphemy
of them which say that they are Jews and
are not
but of the synagogues of Satan
Revelation 3
and9 behold I will make them other
synagogue of Satan which say they are
Jews and are not but do lie behold I
will make them to come and worship
before thy feet and to know that I have
loved thee this has nothing to do with
convert this has something to do with
people who call themselves us or uh uh
who say they are Jews and are not but of
the synagogue or say Satan but your
question is you said that it doesn't
appear to agree with conver to our faith
as Revelation what it doesn't matter
what our thoughts is is what God's
thoughts is let me show you what God's
thoughts is about people who convert the
word convert means in speaking
biblically speaking means to change your
faith or
beliefs let's go to First Timothy the
second chapter first Timothy chapter 2
what are our thoughts our thoughts don't
matter it's what the book
says let's look at what God's thoughts
are and how he feel about converts or
people who because this is what he wants
from all
men two and one 1 Timothy 2 and one we
got to do some reading here real quick
read fast uh we got to read to verse
five go ahead I exort therefore that
first of all supplications pray
intercessor and giving of thanks be made
for all men for all this is Paul to
Timothy all men go ahead for kings and
for all that are in Authority that we
may lead a quiet and peaceful life in
all godliness and honesty go ahead for
this is good and acceptable in the sight
of God our savior yes go ahead who have
all men to be saved and to come into the
N read that again who will have to be
what save there you go go ahead and to
come into the knowledge of the truth and
this and what is the truth well go ahead
for there is one God one mediated
between God and Men the man Christ Jesus
and that's what the whole world got to
convert to the truth and the one Lord
One Faith one baptism one Lord God and
savior of us all I hope that
helped all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered that question
next question
next question Barbara still ask what
type of thermoses can be used to keep
warmth or cold
in is that it and ah yes that question
uh was mentioned when the mother was
talking about water
dispensers or using certain things for
her yeah electricity for her child right
when it came to warming up formula and
the bottles and they want to know you
know what type of thermosets can they
use it looks like they said they've
bought several of them and none of them
seem to work guess
call well like you said at the beginning
we answer biblical
questions that's not in the Bible or she
have to ask somebody else at a different
time all right and we'll keep it moving
on that note to our next question yes
the Bor Walder
says the
scripture mentions many times about
iniquities unrighteousness and sin are
there any difference between
them well they all are evil when you
committing sin iniquity is sin
righteousness is not the right way to
walk and when you talking about Sin Sin
is Sin but let's go into that um Ezekiel
18 Ezekiel 18 and pick up some of those
words Ezekiel
18 asks about iniquity unrighteousness
and sin pick it up at there verse one
and then we go skip down to verse four
and Skip again go ahead the word of the
Lord came unto me again saying verse
four behold All Souls are mine as the
soul of the father so also the soul of
the son is mine the
S go
ahead it shall die all right so the Lord
said behold All Souls are mine soul of
the father and the soul of the son the
the soul that sinth it shall die now
skip down to verse 24 and let's pick up
some of these words because they act
about unrighteousness well opposite of
unrighteousness is righteous and vice
versa verse
24 but when the righteous turneth away
from his righteousness and committeth
iniquity and doeth according to all the
Abomination that the Wicked Man doeth
where shall he live all his
righteousness that he have done shall
not be mentioned in his trespass that he
have trespassed it and in his sin that
he have sined in them shall he
die so we see that we got righteousness
in there opposite of that is unrighteous
and then we see iniquity and we also see
sin in that verse also all three of
these can be against God no doubt about
it but let's go to um Romans 6 Romans
the 6 chapter
and when you get to that Romans 6 just
pick it up at that
verse
11 because the Lord is telling us he
want us be dead unto sin stop sinning
against him some people don't know what
it is right away that's why you need to
stay tuned in with us because we will
definitely teach you what sin is and
that's the transgression of the law
verse 11 go
ahead likewise recom ye also yourselves
to be dead indeed unto sin but alive
unto God through Jesus Christ Our Lord
uhhuh let not sin therefore reign in
your mortal bodies that ye shall obey
the lust thereof
y neither yield ye your members as
instruments of unrighteousness Unto sin
but yield yourselves unto God as those
that are alive from the dead and your
members as instruments of righteousness
unto God so all three of
those iniquities unrighteousness and sin
will get you in trouble with the Lord
that's why you need to know how to walk
with the Lord and keep him happy that's
all I got anybody else want to
add when in first John 5 it says all
unrighteousness is sin yeah
that's correct all unrighteousness is
sin all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next
one our next one Marcelina read as in
Psalms 105 verse
25 could this apply to what's going on
with us and all that are sced this day
and
time all right why don't we go to that
105 brother
tanzel and pick it up at that verse 25
and let's open it up to the panel
because they want to know could this
apply to what's going on with
us go ahead
brother he turned their heart to hate
his people to deal subtility with his
servants open to the panel is this
something that is going on with
us right
now no it's not that's what that's what
happened down in
Egypt back up back up to verse 23 and
read to
26 Israel also came into Egypt and Jacob
soured in the land of ham and he
increased his people greatly and made
them strong with than their enemies he
turned their hearts to hate his people
to deal subtility with his servants and
he said Moses servant and Aaron whom he
had chosen
yeah go
ahead they show his signs among them and
wonders in the land of ham and he sent
darkness and made it dark and they Rebel
not against this
word resten up I just want to let you
know he did that in
Egypt which is in the land of ham on the
African
continent what Israel in
slavery in Egypt before that's where we
grew up to be a nation so we can apply
that to that place and this place only
we just can't use it and spread it
around right true
yeah the book said the Lord turned their
heart
all yeah all right hope that answered
your question next
question next question the air I breathe
ask for you to
explain the
famentera that fent in regards to
whether the Earth is flat or whether
it's
round first thing is the Earth is round
is not flat that's right and and I'm
going to be real nice and and don't tell
you what I think about the people that's
putting that flaw out there it is round
let's go into Isaiah the 4 chapter and
read verses 21 and
22 Isaiah 4021 and
22 have you not known have you not heard
have it not been told you from the
beginning have you not understood from
the foundation of the
earth it is he that sth upon the circle
of the earth and the inhabitant thereof
are his grasshoppers
now that let you know it's round sit up
on the circle of the earth it is round
as far as the fir is concerned let's go
into Genesis the first
chapter and we're going to read the one
and two and then we're going to skip
down you can read it when you get
there in the beginning God created the
Heaven and the Earth and the Earth was
without form and void Darkness was upon
the face of the deep and the spirit of
God moved upon the face of the
waters now skip down to verse six
because what it was when he created the
Heaven Earth it wasn't it was all water
the Earth was submerged in the water now
verse six go ahead and God said let
there be a firmament in the midst of the
waters and let it divide the waters from
the
waters and God made the fir and divided
the waters from
under the firmament from the waters
which were above the firmament and it
was
so and God called the firmament heaven
in the evening and the was the second
day now when God it was this big body of
waters and so the Lord separated the
waters from the water which which is
which he call a f then he called that
form in heaven that's what we see where
the moon and stars and all that above
the Moon the and stars in the planets
you have a great body of water but now
at that particular time under the moon
and stars and and and Sun you had a
great body of water what ver are you
that was in the
eight okay go
ahead and God said let the waters under
the heaven be gathered together un one
place and let the dry land appear and it
was
so uhhuh and God called the dry land
Earth and the Gathering Together of the
waters called he seed and God saw that
it was
good now so the firmament separated two
big bottles of
water and and that fir was called heaven
so when you see your moon and the stars
every down there that is heaven but that
is only one
heaven so we tell you in second
Thessalonians and second Corinthians
rather that there are three Heavens one
is where the where where where the
Father and Jesus and all the Angels
dwell that's above the
uh big body of water which is above the
moon stars and the
son and then the second heaven is where
they preside and the third he and and
and the first Heaven is uh where man
dwell through the Earth is called heaven
and the firmament that where the moon
stars and the uh uh uh sun and the
planets are that's called heaven and
then there is a where the Father and Son
and the angels which is above big body
of water that's above the moon stars and
sun and the planet that is called Heaven
all I have to
say all right thank you for that and if
You' like to further educate your who
ask that question we also have a lesson
called The
Creation all right sister Deborah we
moving on moving on Stephen Gus says in
Matthew 24 verse 29 are the stars that
fell from heaven Angels that's coming
with Jesus or the actual constellation
stars in the
sky all right so then let's go to
Matthew 24 and they want to know are the
stars that fall from Heaven Angels
coming with Jesus the answer to your
first question is no those are not the
Angels that's coming with Jesus but your
second question about the actual are
they the actual constellation stars in
the sky that is correct let's go and
read that Matthew
24 and when you get there brother read
that verse 29
immediately after the tribulation of
those days shall the sun be darkened and
the moon should not give her light and
the Stars shall fall from Heaven and the
powers of the heaven shall be shaped so
we see that immediately after the
tribulation of those days shall the sun
be darken and the moon shall not give a
light and these stars as Fallen are
actual stars from the constellation in
the sky which are stars that the Lord
created let's go to Revelations the 6th
chapter Revelations
6 when you get to that Revelation
6 read 12 and 13 because this is dealing
with that Matthew 24 and 29 they both
tying together go ahead brother and
behold and beheld when he had opened the
Sixth Seal and loow there was a great
Earth earthquake and the sun became
black as sackcloth of hair and the moon
became as blood
uhhuh and the stars of Heaven fell unto
the Earth even as a fig Tre casteth her
untimely figs when she is shaken of A
Mighty Wind so these Stars that's Fallen
actual
constellation that are in the sky
literal stars that you see out there at
night time it's not the angels and
that's all I got
and we hope that that answered your
question sister Deborah let's take a
journey in the new
territory yes we are now into tonight's
Q&A for Wednesday August the 7th
2024 norless tape
as where as
who's words did God say may Saul
afraid 1 Samuel
28 uh 1 Samuel 28 verse 20 and again he
says or they say whose words did the
Bible say I asked so 1 Samuel 28 verse
20 who
words did God say may Saul
afraid all right brother Dre can you
share some light on that question yes
absolutely before we work read 1 Samuel
28 and
20 look
Saul went and saw the woman with a
familiar Spirit he didn't get no answer
from God God had no gave him no answer
let's let's go read that let's let's go
start at verse read that verse 20 and we
gonna bag up a little bit go ahead
brother 1st Samuel 28 and
20 then Saul fell straightway all along
on the earth and was so afraid because
of the words of Samuel and there was no
strength in him for he had eaten no
bread all the day nor all the
night now bag up to verse three bag up
and read verse three in the same
chapter go ahead brother now Samuel was
dead and all Israel had lamented him and
buried him in RMA even in his own City
and Saul had put away all those that
have familiar spirits and the Wizards
out of the land now write that in
capital letters in your mind that
Saul that now Samuel was dead he was
dead and all Israel had lamented for him
and buried him in Rama Saul was dead I
mean Samuel was dead and Samuel was
buried and Saul had put out all the
women that had a familiar
spirits and when he did
that them people ran but skip down to
verse six verse six go
ahead and when sa inquired of the Lord
the Lord answered him not neither by
dream nor by Ur nor by Prophets
then Saul unto his servants then said
Saul unto his servants seek me a woman
that have a familiar spirit that I may
go to her and inquire of her and his
servant said to him behold there is a
woman that have a familiar Spirit at
indoor now the Lord told you not to seek
onto them that have familiar spirits
let's go to to Isaiah 8 read verses 19
and 20 Isaiah 8:19 and
20 read that when you get it
brother Isaiah
819 and 20 yes and when they shall say
unto you seek unto them that have
familiar spirits and unto Wizards that
PE and that mutter shall not a people
seek unto their God for the living to
the
dead and to the Lost and to the
testimony if they speak not according to
this word it is because there is no
light in them so Saul sought somebody
that had no light in fact it wasn't
Samuel that came up because Samuel was
dead and buried now let's go look at two
witnesses that speak about the dead here
let's go to ecclesiastics 9 and we GNA
read verses 56 and 10 Ecclesiastes 9
vers 5 6 10 and I got one more place
after that go ahead brother for the
living know that they shall die but the
dead know not anything neither have they
anymore reward for the memory of them is
forgotten also if you talking to the
dead they not hearing you
right that's a familiar Spirit that's
what the book
say go ahead brother also their love
and their hatred and their Envy is now
perished neither have they any more
portion forever in anything that is done
under the son skip down to verse
10 whatsoever thy hand findeth to do do
it with thy might for there is no work
nor device nor knowledge nor wisdom in
the grave whether thou goest so Samuel
went into the grave and they buried him
and there was no knowledge that he had
nor WI
nor
work where he went now let's go to job
14 and this is it Job
14 Job 14 and read verse
10 job
141 and we gonna skip to
12ad
brother but man dieth and waste of away
yeah man give up The Ghost and where is
he skip down to 12
so man lith down and riseth not till the
heavens be no more they shall not rise
until the heavens be no more until they
roll back like a
scroll skip down to verse
21 and nor be raised out of their
sleep verse 21 his sons came to honor
and he knoweth it not and they are
brought low but he receive it not of
yeah he he don't have no perception of
it because he is
sleep and he will be there until the
resurrection so all that capital letters
about Samuel's talking and all that
that's not the case that was a familiar
spirit I hope that
helps let me throw one more scripture in
there yes sir just tell it straight out
let's go into 1 Chronicles the 10th
chapter and read verse 13 1 Chronicles
10 and
13 first Chronicle
10 so Saul died transgression which he
committed against the
Lord even against the word of the Lord
which he kept not and also for asking
counsel of one that had familiar Spirit
to inquire
of they're asking counsel of one that
had a familiar Spirit to inquire of
it sir that's what she that's who she
inquired
of the counsel of a familiar
Spirit okay that's all I have to
say all right hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one
yes uh Ed R cmore asks in job 25 verse 6
how much less man then that is a worm
and the son of man which is a
worm brother
Jerome yeah um let's go to that verse
and read it again because he pretty much
just quoted what the verse said in the
question
job 25 and verse
6 how much less man that is a worm and
the son of man which is a word yeah if
you uh it's it's a
metaphor uh in regards to what man is in
the sight of God in regards to verse
four and
five so read verse four and
five how then can man be justified with
God or how can he be clean that is born
of a woman behold even to the moon and
it shineth not yeah the stars are not
pure in his eye in his
sight goad how much less man that is a
worm and the son of man which is a
worm yeah so in in God's sight we ain't
pure he said there ain't a man that
don't sin a't man ain't righteous if you
ain't got Jesus you ain't got no
righteousness until he forgive you of
them sins then you can walk in some
Commandments and and and and and hope
that that blood keep you clean in God's
sight you know other than that you ain't
pure you you just dirt you even a worm
in his sight right you know that's a
metaphor that's all I
got all right
thank you for that as we move on to our
next question yes charlot ask on the day
of atonement can you eat drink
medication or drink water with your
medication all right brother Julius what
you say I say what uh yes you can you
mentioned in this question medication
twice you mentioned it twice can you eat
on the day of atonement uh don't
that's you can eat you can take your
medication because we have people that
are sick and we have people that are on
medication and sometimes this medication
on your label it will tell you take with
water and or and it would tell you take
with food that only may be done of you
because you have to have
it that's all I got
all right moving on to our next question
moving on tro uh Troy Barber asks will
animals be around when Jesus returned
and we
are risen after the Thousand Year of
judgment all right brother Julius what
you say answer is yes and we don't know
let me show you what I'm talking about
let's go to Isaiah the 11th
chapter animals will be
here Isaiah chapter
11 P and we gonna read verse two this is
when the Lord
return this is when the Lord return
Isaiah 11 and2 and then we G to
skip when you get it brother go ahead
Isaiah 11 and2 go ahead and the spirit
of the Lord shall rest upon him the
spirit of wisdom and understanding the
spirit of counsel and might Spirit of
knowledge and of the fear of the Lord
this when the Lord come back this is
what Jesus gonna have he gonna have all
these attributes skip down to verse six
go ahead and the Wolf also shall dwell
with the lamb the wolf is an animal this
is when the Lord return the lamb is an
animal he'll be here go ahead and the
leper shall lie down with the kid the
leper going to be here the baby goat
going to be here go ahead and the Cal
and the Young Lion the baby cow and the
lion shall be here go ahead and the
fatling together and a little child
shall leave there go ahead and the cow
and the bear shall
feed shall feed their young ones shall
lie down together and the lion shall eat
straw like the ox and the lion shall eat
straw like the ox Lions don't eat straw
lions eat meat so the Lord going to make
a covenant with with the animals go
ahead and the suckling child shall play
on the hold of the ass the ASP is a the
snake he'll be here but the Lord Look
What the Lord said about it go ahead and
the wean child shall put his hand on the
cockatrice there a cockatrice is a
deadly poison the snake go
ahead they shall not hurt nor destroy in
all my holy mouths for the Earth shall
be full of the knowledge of the Lord as
the waters cover the sea
so now that's when the Lord come and
it's going to be a thousand years of
peace and Tranquility on this Earth but
after the you can go to Revelation the
20th chapter it will tell you that the
rest of the de it don't mention the
animals so we don't know all I can know
all I know is what I can read here that
the animals will be here he gonna take
the wildness out of them and that's the
best I can do with that anybody else got
something all right
hope that answered your question sister
Deborah next question with a Time Check
Yes the time is
8:37 Ben Elf ask is it correct that a
liac and Boaz are descendants of
Judah also are the moabites descendants
of
Ruben all right guest caller take it
from there
yes lonac and
baz uh come out of
Judah but the
moabites they didn't come out of reuben
reuben is one of the tribes of Israel
the moabites came out of lot Abraham's
nephew Abraham's brother's son so the
moabites and and and and and and the
ammonites came out of them because after
the Lord destroyed Sodom and
gomor and the angels get lot and his
wife and his two daughters out of Sodom
and gamar but his wife looked back once
they had gotten out and turned into a
pillar of salt and then lot's two
daughters said that our father don't
have no seed so they got him drunk and
both of them slept with him one had a
son they called Aman and the other one
they called had a son they called Moab
so they the moabites are the children of
lot not
reuben reuben is one of the sons of
Israel
andaz and the other and MC they are out
of the tribe of
Judah that's
it all right well that answered your
question is we Contin continue to move
on All Right Moving On on joy as in
Matthew 19:
16-19 Jesus told the Rich Young Ruler to
keep the Commandments in order to have
eternal life but Jesus only mentioned
the last six why didn't Jesus include
the first four that tells us how to love
God all right what about the first four
of The Commandments in that Matthew 1916
through 19 brother
Jerome when you when you get an
understanding uh God's word you know
that the other Commandments are included
and I'm going read to you why I say that
let's go to um Matthews chapter 22 verse
34-40 you get it go ahead and
read Matthew 22
34-40
yeah but when the Pharisees had heard
that he had put the Sadducees to silence
they were gathered together then one of
them which was a lawyer asked him a
question tempting him and saying but
Master which is the great commandment in
the
law and Jesus said unto him thou shall
love the Lord thy God with all thy heart
with all thy soul and with all thy mind
this is the first and great commandment
and the second is like unto it thou
shall love thy neighbor as
thyself so on these two Commandments
hang all the law and
Prophets yeah so if you loving God
you're gonna keep all the Commandments
that's associated with loving God and if
you loving your neighbor you keeping all
the Commandments associated with loving
your neighbor right you read Ten
Commandments you'll see the ones
associated with loving God and you also
see the ones associated with loving your
neighbor so you got we got to keep them
all that's all I throw something in
there brother Corel yeah go ahead in
that Matthew the 19th Chapter Jesus gave
you the answer he gave you the answer he
said good Master what must I do to enter
into life right let's go we at Matthew
19 read verse 17 look at your answer and
he said unto him why callest thou me
good there is none good but one that is
God but if thou will enter into life the
Commandment
how many Commandments did he give us he
gave us 10 so he just named six but he
the 10 the 10 are the other four are
already there the other four is already
there he said keep the Commandments he
just happened to Name six why because
you can't add to the word or you can't
take away from the word that's all I
got all right hope that anwers your
question as we continue to move on yes
sister Tanisha asked for you to explain
judges
19: 23 through
25 uh she says I know that sodomy and
homosexuality is an abomination in sin
but how is it but how is sending the
Levites concubine out for the men to go
into her and abuse her all night until
her death
justifiable is it preferred for man to
save himself over woman when it comes to
sodomy all right we open that up for the
panel and I see they want to go in there
judges
19 verse
23 23 to 25 25 yes okay so tanzel go
ahead and read it open to the panel and
um go ahead and the man the Master of
the House went out unto them and said
unto them nay my brethren nay I pray you
do not so wickedly seeming that this man
is come into my house do not
defol behold here is my daughter a
maiden and his concubine then will I
bring out now and humble ye them and do
with them what seeth good unto you but
unto this man do not so V
thing because they was trying to get at
this man here and commit an act of Sodom
Tre go ahead but the men would not
hearken to him so the man took his
concubine and brought her forth unto
them and they knew her and abused her
all the night until the morning and when
the day began to Spring they let her
go and sister Deborah the last part of
that question and then the guest caller
look like he want to weigh in on that
all right uh so the question
is is it preferred
so for the man to go into her and abuse
her until uh until her death is that uh
justifiable he's uh she's asking and
also is it preferred for man to save
himself over woman when he comes to
sodomy but the whole thing is yeah
that's the question is it
justifiable I can't answer that question
all I can say is it happened the way it
happened and it say should a man put
himself uh
over a woman let's look at this
situation the first thing if you find
out the woman had uh committed adultery
and she had ran away from this
guy and he went and the second thing is
the guy offered his virgin daughter
along with this man's wife but you
notice the virgin daughter didn't go
maybe the Lord had a hand in
that and the woman had already committed
adultery and he had to go get
her so now whether it's
justifiable you have to ask the Lord
he's the one that permitted it and
whether the man threw the woman out
there before himself well I don't know
the mindset of that man but a lot of men
will not put their woman in danger they
go out and deal with it themselves
that's the all I can the only way I can
answer
that and also brother Cornel it all and
all the books say all these things is
given for our admonition and it shows
you the the uh the
man mindset but it also showed you the
the mindset of the people that was round
about that and it showed us the
wickedness of the mindset of the people
also
yeah all right hope that answered your
question sister Deborah we moving
on yes moving on uh Ben E says when
Assyria took the northern kingdom and
everything surrounding Jerusalem is
there scripture to indicate why they
left the southern Kingdom it's odd it
was left by Assyria until
later where it was taken by Babylon
Babylon okay let's uh guess caller
go they tried to take you to two but the
Lord sent one Angel out there and kill
the
Army
yeah you know so because they talking
about the talking about how the syrians
they taking out
Samaria you know and uh uh uh maybe
somebody can find and read that right
quick where the Lord sent an angel out
there and killed the Assyrian army when
they had uh uh uh when when uh uh uh the
Syrian had cage
Z zon like a
bird somebody find that right
quick all right and search mode for that
right
now King at that time with
sakar
yeah all right search mode she'll be
having it
shortly sound like Second Kings
uh 19 18 18
that's 2 Kings 19 and
35 what you say 19 and 35 Second Kings
19 to the point and verse
35 okay I want to show you
uh that this were the Assyrians trying
to take
Judah and he and and the uh uh his
captain talk real crazy and the Lord
dealt with let's see what one you said
35 let's see that's when he killed
185,000 men yeah that verse 32 talks
about the king of Assyria he should not
come into this city nor shoot an arrow
there right uhhuh sure that was the king
of Syria was trying to take Judah
okay yeah that would be that verse 32
then yeah start at verse
32 therefore thus sayith the Lord
concerning the king of Assyria he shall
not come into this city nor shoot an
arrow there nor come before it with
Shield nor cast a bank against it by the
way that he came by the same shall he
return and shall not come into this city
sayith the Lord but I will defend this
city to save it for my own sake and for
my servant David's sake and it came to
pass that night that the angel of the
Lord went out and smoked in the camp of
the syrians 1004 score and 5,000 when
they arose early in the morning behold
they were all dead
corpse now so that's why the syrians
didn't take Judah the Lord wanted them
to take Samaria if you go and you read
it but then he didn't want them to take
Judah and so the syrians tried to take
them to God sent one Angel and kill a
whole Army and Then followed the Nar rib
and had his own Sons kill him yeah okay
that's why he didn't take it the Lord
didn't want
him and can we go read
uh uh First Kings 11 one of the reasons
why didn't Lord wouldn't allow him to
take Judah what he promised
David you know about about leaving that
one tribe
yeah um
1132 and Skip down read
36 First Kings 11:32 and Skip down read
36 but he shall have one tribe for my
servant David's sake and for Jerusalem's
sake the city which I have chosen out of
all the tribes of
Israel and unto his sons will I give one
tribe that David my servant may have a
light always before me in Jerusalem the
city which I have chosen me to put my
name there yeah and that City had to
remain too because Jesus had to come
first and do what he was supposed to do
to reconcile man back to God so it had
to be there they couldn't let him take
it yeah yeah yeah but the Babylonians
took it there was a little more to it
than that because the Babylonian took it
and then Ezra them went back under the
Persian
Kingdom
okay so the best answer for that
question is they didn't take Judah
because the Lord had an angel kill their
army no doubt the Babylonians took them
out okay that's it all
right hope that answered your question
there sister Deborah time is a ticking
probably got time for one or two more
open Panel questions yeah probably two
more here goes uh chosen girl says I
have family members who believe we
should be planning to move out of the
Cities into rural areas with lik minded
families and friends to be completely
out of this Babylonian system until
we're delivered out by the doing or hand
of God said if we stay among th uh those
who are worldly then we may suffer God's
Wrath along with them and they give
reference
Jeremiah
57 verse 6 and they want some
explanation
Jeremiah 51 verse 6
51 yes Jeremiah 51 verse6 well yes all
right let's go to tanzel but I don't
know where it is that they say they can
go the Gentiles are running it all until
the times of the Gentiles be fulfilled
so where you going to escape
to I don't see where but Jeremiah 51 and
verse 6 tzel then let's open it up to
the
panel please out of the midst of Babylon
and deliver every man his soul be not
cut off in her iniquity for this is the
time of the Lord's Vengeance and he will
Render unto her
recompense now he is not that is not
talking about leaving the city and going
to the country he tell you to
flee I'm me show you what it mean go to
Revelation 12 chap
happen and read about this
woman and see what happened after she
had the
Manchild and see what happened what did
what did she
do uh pick it up at uh verse
13 first revelation 12:1 first to show
you go this woman talking about Israel
go ahead and there appeared a great
woman in Heaven A Woman clothes with the
sun and the moon under her feet and upon
her head a crown of 12
stars and she
being and she being with child cry
travailing in birth and pain to be
delivered and there appeared another
Wonder in heaven now listen and and and
paying to be delivered so
now let's see what happen who she bring
forth skip down to verse five and
continue she brought forth a
Manchild who was the rule all nations
with a rod of iron and their child was
caught up unto God and to his
throne and I let you know woman with
Israel and Jesus came through Israel and
he went back to heaven but now we're
going to go to the last the final days
the day of the Lord what's what's the
woman going to do now go ahead and the
woman fled Into the Wilderness where she
had have a place prepared of God and
they shall feed her there
1,2003 score
days so now that's that the Wilderness
is called a place of safety that's what
he's talking about there was that in
Jeremiah but as far as what are telling
this sister about going in the rural
area and get and get some land of tell
you something I've been around a long
time every Hebrew Israelite Camp wanted
to buy them a
farm they went out and they bought farms
and and uh now they did the children are
the lost the
farm and we're still here in
captivity so to go out and start buying
some place in the rural area living in a
rural area that is older than the person
that asked the question and the one
that's suggesting that must be an old
person that have amn
we tried that it didn't
work don't I have to
say all right and Cornell the scriptures
say in Matthew and in Luke if you try to
run to save your life you gonna lose
it yeah but that f is talking about
Jemiah is talking about when he said the
day of the Lord didn't yeah that's and
and and what come before the day of the
Lord the Great
tribulation the abomination of
desolation and the Lord said when you
see him standing in the Holy place that
is in the temple that's going to be
built in Jerusalem flee but he have a
place prepared for you it's
called
yeah y all right hope that answered your
question sister Deborah next one yes uh
Jeffrey Meyers says the minister
stated during class that the devil can
bless you please
enlighten all
right it was stated that the devil can
bless you please
enlighten all right well let's go into
Luke four that's one place go ahead
guess
caller oh go ahead go ahead you got it
all right let's go into that Luke 4
and this is when Jesus is having a
conversation um with the devil
here and he was being
tempted because the Lord had fasted so
let's see what happened here because he
had fasted for 40 days and Satan came to
have a conversation with the Lord so
let's pick it up at that verse um five
verse four verse
four Luke 4 and four go ahead
and Jesus answered him saying it is
written that man should not live by
bread alone but by every word of God
uhhuh and the devil taking him up into a
high mountain showed unto him all the
kingdoms of the world in the moment of
time all the kingdoms of the world these
are some rich kingdoms you got too and
what did he say the devil said unto him
all this power will I give thee and the
glory of them for thy it is delivered
unto me and to whosoever I will I give
it oh it was delivered unto him to be
able to give it to other people
whomsoever he will guess
caller and that's what's going on but if
you receive if you take him if Jesus
taking him up on it or either we taking
up on it we might get rich we might have
whole lot of things going on in Earth
but the whole thing is when Satan bless
you you going to end up being cursed
forever in the Lake of Fire so the Lord
tell you cannot serve God and man right
all satan can offer you is materal
stuff but if you accept it you that
blessing is actually going to be a curse
because you're going to end up in the
Lake of Fire yes sir can't
serve can't serve two
masters offer money God offer you
eternal life on the good side of the
king
that's
right yep and that is true and sister
Deborah since I know this our last
question Andel let's go to Psalm 73
let's see what David said about these
people in this good old Wicked blessed
situation
here pick it up verse one and read it
brother go
ahead Psalm 73 and
truly God is good to Israel even to such
as are of a clean heart
uhhuh oh yeah but as for me my feet were
almost gone and my steps had well not
slipped but I was EnV at the foolish and
when I saw the prosperity of the
wicked but there are no bands in their
dep but their strength is firm they are
not in trouble as other men neither are
they plagued like other men yeah so just
I just wanted to read that because David
was saying his foot almost slipped when
he saw how much the wicked was proos
prospering and everything seem to be
going right for them until he saw the
end and what was going to become of
them so we yeah Satan is a blesser too
you have to make sure you don't get your
foot caught naturally trap might end up
paying for it
forever right that book say what is it
to gain the whole world and lose your
soul right that's it brother that's what
it say yeah profit you nothing so all
right sister Deborah time check the time
is
9:02 we have ran out of time and we want
to thank everybody from all around the
world who sent in their questions and we
took Joy in answering those questions
and we want to say unto everybody that
if you submitted a question and we
didn't have opportunity to get to it
don't resubmit sister Deborah take your
question put it in rotation and we will
deal with that question next Wednesday
so until we all come together again be
safe out there be blessed and may the
Lord have mercy on us all T close us out
Our Father which are in heaven Hallowed
be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done in earth as it is in heaven give us
this day our daily bread and forgive us
of our debts as we forgive our debt to
us and lead us not into temptation but
Deliver Us from Evil for thine is the
kingdom and the power and the glory
forever in Jesus name we pray amen amen
amen good night all